[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name for fire sacrifice?", "correct_answer": "Immolation", "incorrect_answers": ["Infiltration", "Impregnation", "Innovation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many US states border the Gulf of Mexico?", "correct_answer": "5", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "3", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What African American actor starred as Sidney Deane in the 1992 movie White Men Cant Jump?", "correct_answer": "Wesley Snipes", "incorrect_answers": ["Eriq La Salle", "Will Smith", "Denzel Washington"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "John Bender", "correct_answer": "The Breakfast Club", "incorrect_answers": ["Weird Science", "Class Reunion", "Sixteen Candles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the Looney Tunes cartoons, there was a little bird who was always trying to catch Foghorn Leghorn,  Whats the name of this brave little brown bird?", "correct_answer": "Henery Hawk", "incorrect_answers": ["Yoyo", "Booker T.", "Sid the Sparrow"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was Cleon doing after the war in the movie Dead Presidents?", "correct_answer": "preaching", "incorrect_answers": ["pimping", "bagging grocery", "drugs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This word is Sanskrit for Great Soul, and is used like the title Saint. Some believe that it was first used in 1915 when speaking of Ghandi.", "correct_answer": "Mahatma", "incorrect_answers": ["Master", "Mehta", "Mohandas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The 40 Year-Old Virgin, Andy has a framed rock poster on the wall. What rock group is depicted on the poster ?", "correct_answer": "Asia", "incorrect_answers": ["REO Speedwagon", "Journey", "Led Zeppelin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The production of the 2007 movie Spider-Man 3 was one of the priciest in film history. What does Toby Maguires character study at the Columbia University?", "correct_answer": "Physics", "incorrect_answers": ["Zoology", "Chemistry", "Photography"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The island of New Guinea was named after the country of Guinea. Which is Guinea located?", "correct_answer": "Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["In the Pacific Ocean", "South America", "Asia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the first name of Dan Akroyds character in the 1988 movie The Great Outdoors?", "correct_answer": "Roman", "incorrect_answers": ["Gene", "Roger", "Richard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The combination of which perfume notes comprises the so-called main theme of a perfume?", "correct_answer": "Middle and base notes", "incorrect_answers": ["Top, middle and base notes", "Top and base notes", "Top and middle notes"]}]